answerly.com 2012-07-23

# InboxQ

## Privacy Policy

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, InboxQ collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. InboxQ's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how InboxQ's visitors use its website. From time to time, InboxQ may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

InboxQ also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. InboxQ does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to InboxQ's websites choose to interact with InboxQ in ways that require InboxQ to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that InboxQ gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.

At present we use Twitter as our identification provider. Any use of Twitter on behalf of the individual is subject to the Twitter Terms of Service and Twitter Privacy Policy. InboxQ collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor's interaction with InboxQ. InboxQ does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to authenticate with Twitter, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
InboxQ may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. InboxQ does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. InboxQ uses Google Analytics, Chartbeat and Mixpanel to help collect information about site usage. These services collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Their usage of this information is governed by their privacy policies. Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

InboxQ discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on InboxQ's behalf or to provide services available at InboxQ's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using InboxQ's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

InboxQ will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organisations, as described above, InboxQ discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when InboxQ believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of InboxQ, third parties, or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a InboxQ website and have supplied your email address, InboxQ may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with InboxQ and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. InboxQ will also send you transactional email that you opted into, at the frequency you requested, you can unsubscribe from these at any time. InboxQ reserves the right to introduce new types of transactional mail which you can then change the frequency of or unsubscribe if you so choose.

InboxQ would like to reassure you that we will be respectable with the permissions you grant us with your Twitter authentication. We will never access your direct messages stored against your Twitter account. We will never post to Twitter without your explicit permission for us to do so.

InboxQ takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. InboxQ uses cookies to help InboxQ identify and track visitors, their usage of InboxQ website, and their website access preferences. 

InboxQ visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using InboxQ's websites, with the drawback that certain features of InboxQ's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, InboxQ may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at InboxQ's sole discretion. InboxQ encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## Contact Us

Need help? [Visit our forum](http://www.getsatisfaction.com/inboxq/)

For everything else, email[ joe@inboxq.com](mailto:joe@inboxq.com) or call (855) 3-INBOXQ
